[{"Question":" In which menu is the command to insert headers and footers available?","option 1":" File","option 2":"Insert","option 3":" Format","option 4":" Edit","answer":" Insert"},{"Question":" To print a document, press ..............then press Enter.","option 1":"Ctrl + N","option 2":"Shift + P","option 3":"Ctrl + M","option 4":"Ctrl + 0","answer":"Shift + P"},{"Question":"What is the default file extension used by Excel 2016 and later versions?","option 1":".xls","option 2":".xlsx","option 3":".xlsm","option 4":".xlsb","answer":".xlsx"},{"Question":"Which area in Excel displays the active cell address?","option 1":"Status Bar","option 2":"Formula Bar","option 3":"Name Box","option 4":"Ribbon","answer":"Name Box"},{"Question":"Which feature would you use to capture and analyze data from multiple sheets into one sheet?","option 1":"PivotTable","option 2":"Data Form","option 3":"Consolidate","option 4":"Template","answer":"Consolidate"},{"Question":"What is the quickest way to resize a column to fit its contents?","option 1":"Double-click the column header","option 2":"Drag the header","option 3":"Right-click and select resize","option 4":"Use Format options","answer":"Double-click the column header"},{"Question":"How would you quickly find all cells in a worksheet that contain formulas?","option 1":"Use Find feature","option 2":"Filter by color","option 3":"Go to Special","option 4":"Use Trace Precedents","answer":"Go to Special"},{"Question":"You need to track changes made by team members on an Excel workbook. What feature should you use?","option 1":"Track Changes","option 2":"Audit Trail","option 3":"Revision History","option 4":"Document Inspector","answer":"Track Changes"},{"Question":"How can you split text from one cell into multiple columns?","option 1":"Use Text to Columns feature","option 2":"Use DIVIDE()","option 3":"Use SPLIT() function","option 4":"Use SEGMENT()","answer":"Use Text to Columns feature"},{"Question":"How do you link data from a cell in one worksheet to another worksheet within the same workbook?","option 1":"Use the Link feature","option 2":"Type the cell reference directly","option 3":"Use a hyperlink","option 4":"Use a formula","answer":"Type the cell reference directly"}]
